friends today we will speak in Russian
друзья сегодня будем по-русски Потому
Because we want to send a lot of
что э хотим закинуть очень много э
good thoughts to people from the Russian
хороших мыслей э людям из Российской
Federation from the forced peoples to the Yakuts to the Chechens
Федерации из подневольных народов якутам
insha Tatars Bashkort and
чеченцами иншам татаром башкортом и
others visiting today Oleg Magovetsky
другим в гостях сегодня Олег маговецкий
representative of the forum of free peoples what is the
представитель форума свободных народов
main idea form
в чём основная идея форма
the main idea form is  creating
основная идея форма - это создание
roadmaps for real planned actions
дорожных карт реальных плановых действий
because the process of the
потому что процесс
final dismantling of the Moscow
окончательного демонтажа Московской
Empire is already underway; what began in
империи он уже идёт то что начал с 1917
1917 continued in 1991 and, due to the decision of
году продолжилось в 1991 и из-за решения
war criminals and terrorists, was greatly
военных преступников террористов очень
accelerated. February 24, 2022 will be
ускорил 24 февраля 2022 года будет
completed in the near future and
завершено ближайшим мнением времени и
our question is  what will happen next,
наш вопрос состоит в том что будет потом
we want to help create a new
мы хотим помочь создать новый
architecture of collective security and the
архитектуру коллективной безопасности и
possibility of a free, comfortable life
возможность свободной комфортной жизни
both for
как для
modern, unfortunately, non-citizens of the
современных к сожалению не граждана
Russian Federation and for
поданных Российская Федерация так и для
all neighbors along the perimeter of this empire and for the
всех соседей по периметру этой империи и
whole world, so we are working to
для всего мира поэтому мы работаем
create a vision for the concepts of the future, I
создавая визию концепты будущего есть я
often communicate
часто общаюсь
with Russians, when I come across
с россиянами когда мне попадается
representatives of different nations,
представители разных народов
independence, they have two main
независимость у них есть два основных
fears that I saw. The first is that
страха которые я видел Первое это что из
they won’t survive from Moscow, that they are not
Москвы они не проживут что они не
subsidized regions, it scares you. And the
дотационные регионы вас пугает Да и
second thing is that if Russia collapses, everyone
второе что если будет распад России все
will start fighting with everyone, uh and  when no,
со всеми начнут воевать э-э и когда нет
for example, yes, that is, they fell apart, they live. How
например да то есть распались живут Как
Russia can
Россия
deal with these fears and
как вот с этими страхами проработать и
how work is already being done in this
как уже ведётся работа в этом
direction so that at the time of the collapse of the
направлении чтобы э в момент краха
Russian Moscow Empire,
российской Московской империи
these peoples could have
москвинской эти народы смогли
economic articles and If there were no
экономические статьи и Если бы не было
conflicts, Russia Moscow would play on their
конфликтов Россия Москва играла на их
national  the contradiction of your questions
национальных противоречие ваших вопросах
is a significant part of the answer, even
есть значительная часть ответа даже то
the way you started our conversation is
как как вы начали наш разговор
approximately this colonial name We
Примерно это колониальное название Мы
all live Unfortunately, including in
все живем К сожалению и в том числе
English, that is, in fact, these are
английским языком да то есть по сути это
occupied nations by Muscovy We live
оккупированные нации московией Мы живем
in those propaganda myths that have not been around for
в тех мифов пропаганды которые не
centuries  only inside your
столетиями а не только во внутрь а своей
empire, but also outside, but it brings it into your head and it
империи но и вне а вносит в голову и это
became the norm once. There you repeat a lie a million times and
стало нормы когда-то Там миллион раз
you back it up with billions of gold and
подкрепляешь миллиардами там золотых а
then not gold, unsecured
потом и не золотых необеспеченных
standard American dollars, it
стандартном американских долларов это
begins to live its own life and the
начинает жить своей жизнью и
first  question about the subsidization of
первый вопрос по поводу дотационности
failure Yes, this is what they say according to
неуспешности Да такое говорят по
Russian statistics, and the Republic of Sakha
российской статистике а Республика Саха
exists, and the
есть а
Republic of Sakha occupies 3 million square
Республика Саха занимает 3 млн квадра
kilometers, a little less than a million
километра немножко меньше миллиона
people, it is one of the diamond capitals of the
населения есть одно из алмазных столиц
world that has oil, gold, they
мира которые есть нефть золото они
simply have it, it is mined and sold there,
просто есть она добывается продается там
China,
Китай
it is only up to the Jura.  subsidized
она только до Юра есть дотационный
because the companies that carry out
потому что компании которые осуществляют
mining, including
добычу в том числе
just Moscow and so on,
просто там Московскую и так далее
so in fact, the Republic of Sakha is
поэтому самом деле Республика Саха это
Northern Qatar, relatively speaking, yes, that is,
Северный Катар условно говоря да то есть
most likely the
скорее всего
eternal abomination will interfere here, but in the
может тут помешает вечный мерзота но в
next 30 years the highest
следующие там 30 лет самые высокие
knowledge in the world will be far from  in the
знания в мире будут далеко не в
Persian Gulf Yes, they arise there in
Персидском заливе Да возникают там в
Yakutsk, they will arise in Novosibirsk,
Якутске будут возникать в Новосибирске
Krasnoyarsk, and so on. Because
Красноярске и так далее Потому что
most regions, most
большинство регионов большинство
regions, they
регионов они
are not economically surplus, it’s
экономические есть не профицитными это
just a
просто вопрос
dirty question from the point of view of where
грязных с точки зрения куда прописано
the jurisdiction is registered. Yes, in simple words, they
юрисдикция Да есть простыми словами
take money from the federal budget, 100
забирают деньги федеральный бюджетом 100
rubles, and the duration of the federal
рублей а длительность федерального
budget 50, well, like a company that
бюджета 50 ну типа компанию которая
earned money, it is no longer that is, really
заработал она уже не то есть реально
pseudotations and questions, again, that
псевдотации и вопросы опять же в чем что
regions are not important, republics and regions
регионы не важны республики и области
are colonies Yes, today Moscow is a
это колонии Да сегодня Москва - это
metropolis, the
метрополия
Russian Federation is not a Federation only
Российская Федерация не Федерация только
in words, a real
в словах реальная
Secret, and from absolutely different peoples
Тайна причём с разных абсолютно народов
different and it uses
абсолютно разных и она использует
resources and nothing comes in return. And there are
ресурсы и ничего не идёт взамен А есть
regions that are not in such a good light
регионы которые в не таком хорошем свете
right away, for example, or
сразу например или
Buryatia or Siberia, which is independent, which is
Бурятии или Сибирь независимая у которой
actually doing poorly now, and their
в действительности сейчас плохо а-а и их
internal budget is in deficit Well, like
внутренний бюджет он дефицит Ну и типа
Moscow Although not Moscow, but that  they sat and
Москва Хотя не Москва а та же сидели и
so on
так далее
makes a certain subsidy in
делает определённую дотацию на
the territory. But why is this because
территории Но почему так потому что
these regions of the republics, for example, are
этими регионами республиками например
often remembered for the
часто вспоминается
successful economic
успешным экономически
transport opportunities of the resources of a
транспортных возможностей ресурсов
large domestic market of
большого внутреннего рынка
tourism potential? Regardless,
туристического потенциала Независимо
Dagestan will be economically successful; the
Дагестан будет экономически успешным
question is that now the leadership is
вопрос в том что сейчас руководство
institutional, that is, management
институционально то есть менеджмент
occurs topics people who  interested in
происходит темы люди кто заинтересован в
wealth in the development of their people of their
богатстве в развитии своего народа своей
country, and the Moscow stavriki who
страны а московскими ставриками которые
come to the colony as vice-governors,
приезжают в колонию как вице-губернаторы
looking at their loot, they worked out
они смотрящие свои бабло отработали
how much they were paid there, they
сколько их там заплатили в Кремль
brought them to the Kremlin to be appointed anyway,
занесли чтобы их назначили все равно они
on the contrary, they are, on the contrary, not interested
наоборот более того не заинтересованы
in people being poor so that they  there
чтобы люди были бедными чтобы у них не
was no possibility of the middle class when a
было возможности средний класс когда
person develops, well, he moves according to
человек развивается он ну двигается по
convention. Damn, when a person says that
условно Блин когда человек говорит что
there is and there is already where to spend it. Why are we
есть и уже есть куда тратить А почему мы
slaves and of course they don’t want this for me, that’s
рабы и конечно мне этого не хотят
why independent Dagestan, like
поэтому независимые Дагестан как и
all the other states that
пришли все остальные государства которые
were before, you don’t have colonies
были раньше колонии у тебя нет
opportunities to be a budget, you can’t
возможности быть бюджет ты не можешь
constantly spend more, earn more, yes,
постоянно тратить больше зарабатывать да
you can take some kind of a-a in Russian,
Ты можешь брать какие-то а-а на русском
yes, that is, take loans from the IMF There and
языке да то есть брать кредиты МВФ Там и
so on.
так далее
Therefore, you must reduce income and
Поэтому ты должен сводить доходы и
costs, invest human
затраты инвестировать человеческий
capital in attracting investments externally and
капитал в привлекать инвестиции внешне и
you become  developed, there are much
ты становишься развитом есть намного
more complex cases when, after a colony,
более сложные случаи когда после колонии
countries that if we roll back
страны которые если мы там откатаем на
50 years ago and see how the
50 лет назад и посмотрим как распадалась
British French Empire, the Japanese
британская французская Империя японская
Imperialist Empire fell apart
империалистической
in the word Empire, although it is not an Empire, the
в слове Империя хотя она не Империя
Russian Federation is called Although the
Российская Федерация называется Хотя
Federation and at the time there was forty-five
Федерации и на момент там сорок пятого
or even fifty  the fifth island of
года или даже пятьдесят пятого остров
Formosa is a former empire of what we now
Формоза бывший империи то что мы сейчас
call Taiwan or Korea. These were
называем Тайвань или Корея Это были
some of the poorest countries in the world,
самые одни из самых бедных стран в мире
yes. And no one would have become Singapore as a
да И никто бы не стал Сингапур как
former British colony, the military
бывшие британская колония военном
base of the navy, they
базовым военно-морского флота они
imported even though they
импортировали даже вот у них ничего не
had nothing there  limited from the territory there and
было там ограничена с территории там да
now immediately that Singapore had no
сейчас сразу что у Сингапура не было
other way How to become successful here is
другого пути Как стать успешным тут
different, it may not have its own ports there,
другое он может нет там ку своих портов
this is an institution. This is because they
это институция Это потому что
were controlled by me or the horse, other people
управлялись мной или конью другие люди
who understood the fight set up at home,
которые понимали бороться настроили дома
then if you read about the beautiful Memoirs of
то если почитать о прекрасном Мемуары
very Sveta  73 worlds in the first because
очень Света 73 мира в первой потому что
in the Third World when it became independent
в Третьем мире когда стал независим у
they had essentially a Civil War in
них была Гражданская по сути война в
Malaya there were communists there Soviet a
Малая там были коммунисты там Советская
bunch there in Singapore Three different peoples
там куча в Сингапуре Три разных народа
who loved the other very much the Chinese
которые другого очень любили китайцев
in quality management uh
в качественном управлении э-э
education and investment open
образование и инвестиции открытая
economy
экономика
when  became independent, this is the only
когда стало независимой это единственный
example in fact in Africa of countries
пример фактически в Африке страны
that have built a democratic,
которые построила демократическое
economically successful society, although
экономически успешное общество хотя у
they have nothing essentially, that is, they do not
них ничего нет по сути то есть Они не
have access to the sea, they have one and a half
имеют выхода к моря у них полтора
million population, limited with
миллиона населения ограниченность с
different such countries, very
разными такими странами очень
ambiguous, but they could not. For example,
неоднозначными но не смогли А например
at that moment  when you name the countries
за тот момент когда вы называете страны
then South Africa Argentina Iran
то южная Африка Аргентина Иран
Afghanistan especially there South Africa
Афганистан вот особенно там Южная Африка
Argentina Venezuela partly some of the
Аргентина венесуала частично одни из
richest but due to poor
были самых богатыми но из-за плохого
management they are now not
менеджмента управления они сейчас не
the richest and even some of them are not
самые богатые и даже некоторые с них не
average someone guaranteed
средний кто-то гарантировал
one of the largest  And some
одними из самых больших А некоторые
sources have the largest
источники а самыми большими запасами
oil reserves in the world, so the question is whether they will be
нефть в мире поэтому вопрос того будут
successful or not. For many, right away. Yes,
успешны или нет Э для многих сразу Да
because Moscow is now taking away from them; for
потому что Москва сейчас забирает у них
many, it depends on what kind of
для многих зависит от того каких вы
leaders you can choose from which one and the
сможете выбрать себе лидеров из какой а
management of your state. Because
управление своим государством Потому что
now they  right, rather, the poor Yes, and there
сейчас они прямо скорее бедные Да а там
they have a chance to be uh,
у них есть шанс быть э-э
many will have a chance that is
у многих появится шанс которого сейчас
not there now and it’s a strange question Listen, this is not uh
нет и странно вопрос Слушайте это не э-э
sakhiya Siberia urad or St. Petersburg, you can
сахия Сибири ураду или Петербургу можно
Moscow is Moscow needs them, that is, they
Москва это Москве они нужны то есть в
don’t sit in Moscow Where to send ours
Москве не сидят Куда отправить наши
money because if you thought so in
деньги потому что если вы так думали в
Moscow you said listen so let’s
Москве то сказали слушайте так давайте
make the Moscow Republic
сделаем Московскую республику нам
feed us and the fact that it’s just that and I
кормить и факу да это же просто вот и я
already forgot about the mass question But remember
уже забыл про массовый вопрос Но помните
she doesn’t remember either
ей уже тоже не помню
uh here’s another very good one appeared uh
э-э вот ещё очень хороший появился э
Often  we only talk about
Часто у нас говорят только про
independence, we are a republic Yes, but they don’t
независимость нас республика Да но не
consider regionalism in the mass consciousness Yes,
рассматривают в массовом сознании
if we look at
региональности Да если мы смотрим э
this concept, here is the Spanish world Yes, if there is
такое понятие вот испанский мир Да если
a lot of territory of the former cool
куча территории бывшей классной
Spanish crown, which now you
испанской кроны которые сейчас вот вы
know conditionally, Cuba is
знаете условно Куба
better roughly designated a
лучше примерно назначили
bunch of countries that are no different  their
кучу стран которые вот не отличаются они
population is actually all
населением фактически они все
Spanish-speaking, all with some kind of commonality, they
испаноязычные все с какой-то общей там
now live separately, play
сейчас живут отдельно играют в футбол
each other’s football at championships and
друг друга на чемпионатах и развивается
how realistic are the prospects for such
насколько реально перспективы таких
regional projects developing?
региональных проектов
This is a very important point because this
Это очень важный момент потому что этот
Spanish-speaking world is not even Spanish Yes,
испаноязычный мир даже не испанский Да
this is a question of de-colonization,
это вопрос де колонизации все
practically everything  European empires that
практически европейские империи которые
were they went their own way as a
были они прошли собственный путь как
metropolis to demolish their not colonies the
митрополия демплясаться их не колонии
process of where colonization is so now
процесс где колонизации поэтому сейчас
probably no one has a question:
наверное ни у кого не возникает вопрос
can Argentina exist
может существовать Аргентины Чили
side by side with 2 states Argentina This is
рядышком до 2 государства Аргентина Это
not a problem even in Europe we have
не проблема даже в Европе мы имеем
examples besides the colonial aspects on but
примеры кроме колониальных аспектов на а
we have  it’s just for example the Germans they
имеем его просто вот например немцы они
live not only in Germany there are Germans Well
живут не только в Германии есть немцы Ну
relatively speaking as a general Yes they don’t live there
условно говоря как общий Да там не живут
they live in Switzerland they live partly
они живут в Швейцарии они живут частично
there Einstein in Belgium the Netherlands and
там эйнштейне в Бельгии Нидерландах и
so on That is, the question is that one
так далее То есть вопрос того что один
can be or a nation according to the state
сможет быть или нация по государственном
This  the question is de facto, it exists. The second
Это вопрос де-факто он существует второй
point is that I have certain conditions
момент у меня есть определённые условия
that make it even more difficult to work if
которые ещё более трудоспособность если
we perceive Russian and not
мы будем воспринимать русский да не
Russia.
Россия
This Empire is stool for you asakhakh Circassians,
Вам эта Империя табурят асахах черкес
even the most Muscovites do not
даже самые москвичи на имперцы не
perceive them as Russians even if we are
воспринимает их как русских Даже если мы
talking about Russians, if
говорим про русских если
they combine  imagine the finale of the Ugra in the
которые сочетает себе финал Угра в
Mongolian element Tatar elements
монгольский элемент татарские элементы
elements are partially only Slavic
элементы частично всего лишь Славянский
then even this community This is an example of
то даже это сообщество Это пример того
what needs to be done statehood
что необходимо делать государственность
in a Russian Russian walkie-talkie not only can
у русского русской рации не просто может
But now there should be several
А должно сейчас быть несколько
states because one has not yet
государств потому что одна пока не
passed identification and normalization in the
пройдёт идентификации и нормализации в
Russian language Well  yes, politically we
русском языке Ну да политический нас
should have several states and this
должно быть несколько государств и этот
strong region will help everyone
сильный регион он поможет всем быстрее
get through this disease faster, again when the 13
пройти эту болезнь опять же когда 13
colonies that were in North
колоний которые находились Северной
America proclaimed their independence
Америке провозглашают свою независимость
were essentially the same people
были по сути теми же самыми людьми
who
которые
Or suddenly no, she doesn’t understand that they
Или вдруг нет она не понимают что они
want something else they want
хотят другого они хотят заморских
overseas colonies They want to build a new
колоний Вон они хотят построить новое
state with
государство на
a letter and proclaimed their
букву и возгласили свою
United States of America X and the metropolis
Соединенные Штаты Америки X и метрополия
section of the statistical ocean if we
разделом статистический океан если мы
look at ourselves, this is the same
посмотрим на себе это та же самая
colony of Moscow
колония Москвы
just the Ural Mountains And the question
просто Уральскими горами Да и вопрос
of the Independence of Siberia in the format of the
того Независимости Сибири в формате
Siberian Confederation for the United
Сибирская Конфедерации для Соединённых
States there  in Siberia, the Ural Republic of
там штатов в Сибири Уральской республике
Ingria with its capital in St. Petersburg,
ингрии со столицей в санкт-петербурге
this is a question that will help liberate
это вопрос который поможет освободиться
all
всем
the most so title and that is, the
инейшим так звание да то есть
occupied ones will
оккупированным
also be helped by advertising in this process.
тоже поможет рекламные в данном процессе
This will also help the Metropol liberate
Это поможет освободиться и Метрополь
because the sea yes, that is, it is
потому что морское да то есть это
actually there and the territory is a
фактически там а территория это
historical region when  it will lose
исторический регион когда она потеряет
its colonies, including the city of
свои колонии включительно с города
Moscow, they will have a chance to build a
Москва у них появится шанс построить
normal free civilizational
нормальная свободное цивилизационная
Federal society and state, this is
Федеральная общество и государство это
Moscow, this is the Imperial center of
Москва это же Имперский центр
the world city and it can go the same
мировой город и он может пройти тот же
way that Istanbul went after the
путь который прошёл Стамбул после
fall of the Ottoman Empire, for example Vienna
падения Османской империи например Вена
after the fall was
после падение было
[music]
[музыка]
and at that time, in fact, for almost 500 years, the
и на тот момент фактически почти 500 лет
center of imperial Europe was a nightmare. And
центром имперским Европы и кошмарил А
half of central Europe there, a bunch of
половина там центральной Европы кучу
Kuchmen was an even worse situation. Wow,
кучмен был ещё хуже ситуация Ничего себе
these cities were able to find themselves as
эти города смогли себя найти как
tourist financial cultural
туристические финансовые культурные
centers and it’s better not only for their neighbors but also for
центры и лучше не только им соседям но и
those people who live there much
тем людям которые там живут намного
It’s better that Moscow has the same chance,
лучше у Москвы есть такой же шанс
so it’s very important to work and convey to
поэтому очень важно работать и доносить
Muscovites that they don’t need you. The
в том числе москвичам что вам не нужна
Far East is a very clear example, so
Дальний Восток очень яркий пример так
when people wake up there, Muscovites
когда э люди там просыпаются москвичи
only go to bed there, and that
только там условно ложатся спать да то
is, they live at completely different hours,
есть они живут в абсолютно разных часы
absolutely people  from this bridge, also
абсолютно люди из данного моста тоже
Vladivostok, we were more often in Japan in
Владивостока чаще бывали в Японии в
China than in Moscow Yes, they all drive
Китае чем в Москве Да они ездят все там
right-hand drive cars there, that is, uh,
на праворульных тачках то есть э-э по
essentially, if it falls from the sky, well,
сути э им если упадёт с неба так ну
freedom from
Свобода
distant power from intuition will not notice, it
дальней власти от интуиция не заметит
turns out uh, here you are  we remembered an
получается э-э тут вы вспомнили
interesting point: who goes where? I
интересный момент кто куда ездит Я даже
won’t even talk about Khabarovsk
не буду говорить про Хабаровска
Vladivostok if St. Petersburg is listening to us,
Владивосток если нас слушают
then everyone I know
Петербургское то всех которых я знаю они
said that they were more often in Helsinki
говорили что они чаще бывали в Хельсинки
in Tallinn than in Moscow and they wanted to
в Таллине чем в Москве и они хотели там
be there more often because well, excuse me. [ __ ] you
чаще бывает потому что ну извините Иди
Moscow
нахуй Москва
they somehow have no perception,
у них как-то есть не не восприятие опять
again, look at St. Petersburg, it was an imperial
же смотрите Петербург это была имперская
capital, built as an imperial capital,
столица построена как имперская столица
but when it lost its status.
но когда она утратила свой статус В
When the Bolsheviks moved it to Moscow, the St.
когда большевики перенесли его в Москву
Petersburgers took over for themselves, they now took over themselves,
в петербуржцы за себя перешли они сейчас
when even everyone says, St. Petersburg,
себя когда даже все говорят э Петербург
even in Russia.  they are talking about the cultural
даже в России говорят о культурную
page, that is, St. Petersburg has always
страницу то есть Петербург всегда
gone over, now it no longer has such an
перешёл у него сейчас уже нет такого
imperial uh phantom battle So that’s enough,
имперского э-э фантомный бой Так хватит
I’m going back to those cities again
возвращаюсь к тем городами опять же
when you talk about this justification
когда вы будете про это оправдание
so this is again an infection
настолько это опять же инфекция потому
because this is the Far East for Moscow yes For
что это Дальний Восток для Москвы да Для
those  territory future Pacific
тех территория будущее Тихоокеанская
coast Pacific Federation and
побережье Тихоокеанская Федерация и
of course from Vladivostok Hello from the
конечно же из Владивостоке Здравствуй с
regions of the imperial Primorye Amur region
регионах имперской Приморье приамурья
this is essentially Northern Manchuria which,
это по сути Северная Маньчжурия которую
again, the Moscow Empire
опять же Московской империи
took advantage of the weakness of imperial China
использовавшие слабость имперского Китая
when they fought in 15 minutes they simply
когда они воевать за 15 минут просто
took themselves away from what was bad like this
себя забрали то что плохо типа лежал эта
part lay naturally  I am part of
часть она естественным путем я часть
the East in a natural way, this region is
Восточной естественным путем это регион
culturally and economically integrated and
культурно-экономический интегрирован и
it wants to see itself as part of the free
он хочет себя видеть частью свободного
world with Japan, the Republic of Korea, it
мира с Японии республикой Корея это
will be a very rich country, moreover,
будет очень богатая страна более того
it will also be able to help keep the
она сможет еще помочь удерживать
imperial pizzas of the People's
имперские пиццы Китайской Народной
Republic of China and it is very important to talk
Республике и с этим очень важно говорить
and work with this because  Vladivostok is also
и работать потому что Владивосток тоже
not needed Moscow
не нужно Москва
What would you like to wish to the peoples of the
Что вы хотели бы пожелать народам
Russian Federation to the people of the Russian
Российской Федерации людям Российской
Federation who are afraid of
Федерации которые там боятся
Independence?
Независимости
Why did you start, what if Freedom falls
чего вы начали что если упадет Свобода
from somewhere Freedom does not fall can
на откуда-то Свобода не падает может
fall create your own successful state
упасть создать свою успешную государство
now, unfortunately, for a very
сейчас к сожалению на протяжении очень
long time you  you live,
долгого времени вы живёте
moreover, sometimes some people there 10-15
более того иногда какие-то там еще 10-15
years ago This is slavery, wearing what
лет назад Это рабство ношение того что
was 20 ago seemed quite good because
было 20 назад казалось неплохим потому
economically it seems to have become better than it
что экономически вроде стало лучше чем
was in the late 80s and early nineties
было в конце 80 и в начале девяностых
Why did you bring the Soviet Union, but any
Почему привел Советский Союз но любая
Empire ends its moment yours  The
Империя заканчивает свой момент ваша
Empire lives directly, moreover,
Империя живет непосредственно мало того
on the highway, its incredible resources are not for
на трассе свои неимоверные ресурсы не на
you to live better, but to
то чтобы Вы лучше жили а на то чтобы
kill other people and put you in
убивать других людей и вас сажать в
prison, so no matter how afraid you are of the
тюрьмы поэтому Как бы вы не боялись
freedom and responsibility that comes with it,
свободы и ответственности которые несет
Freedom is much better,
свой Свобода это намного лучше более
moreover, it is much safer  than to
того это намного безопаснее чем
continue to be part of a terrorist
продолжать быть частью террористического
state, someone or herbalists
государства кто-то либо травянисты
who already exist, and even more so who will
которые уже есть а тем более которые
come When they die,
придут Когда умрет
they will destroy your your families, you
они будут уничтожать ваш ваши семьи вы
will
будете
Therefore, if you want to have a 10 chance in
Поэтому если вы хотите иметь шанс 10 на
Japanese cars, go on vacation and
японских автомобилях а Ездить отдыхать и
sign up the children so that they learn
расписывать детей чтобы научились
normally in schools.  normal
нормально школах была нормальная
medicine so that your whole world can see you
медицина чтобы ваш весь мир вас видит
guys, forget this
ребята забудь такое
Oksimiron is like the Russian Federation,
Оксимирон как Российская Федерация
become, as one war
становитесь как говорил один военный
criminal said, the Urals, the
преступник уральцами московиками
Muscovites, the Siberians for your freedom
сибиряками за ваши свободу
[music]
[музыка]
YouTube driving us into a
YouTube загоняя нас через кардиорке в
shadow ban through cardiorek and a very rich appearance is not
теневый бан и дужебогатого вида не
shown to people in private,
показывается людям в частном на
information about is shown  streams in order
показывается информация про стримы тому
for a little operational zazok
для того чтобы мало оперативный зазок
to subscribe right at a time and try there in a
подпишется прям за раз а попыт там в
kilogram about Cream video
килограмме о Крим видео
information and we are with you on a stylish
информация и мы с вами по стильной
operational star
оперативной звездок
we will show you the YouTube word of Ukraine
это покажем вам YouTube слово Украине